I’m from Ukraine, the city of Khmelnitsky, and where are you
я из украины город хмельницкий а вы
from from Russia,
откуда из россии
Kislovodsk Kislovodsk, and so the Caucasus is
кисловодск кисловодск а так кавказ да
strong,
сильный
you look, I ask people from Russia
вы смотрите я у людей из россии
and they can deceive such a thing to the heights in
спрашиваю и такую вещь к вершинам в
Ukraine, they
украине могут обманывать нам
tell us that the Ukrainian army
рассказывают что украинская армия
drove the Russian army completely from the
прогнала российскую армию полностью из
Kharkov region and with shame the
харьковской области и с позором
Russian  the army abandoned the equipment, it
российская армия побросала технику
fled, it can deceive us, it can
бежала может нас обмануть может мне
tell me what they say on TV,
сказать что у вас по телевизору говорят
I don’t turn on the TV yet, and the same
я пока не включён телевизор и тот же
week it’s like a week, but we hear
неделю it неделе вроде а мы а там слышу
some kind of information
какой-то информацию
there and that the
владеют и что
regrouping of Russian troops is going and
перегруппировка российских войск идёт и
where are they  regrouped
куда они перегруппировались
there somehow to be called .
там как-то назвать .
very much left of the schools and the crossings regrouped without
очень и переправ перегруппировались без
heavy equipment abandoned heavy
тяжелой техники побросали тяжелую
equipment
технику
say the
сказать
army men they are not the views of the army men yes and you are
армейцы они не взгляды армейцы да а вы
special Ukrainians like you are also
украины специальных как тоже
interested in yes I am interested
заинтересованы в да я заинтересована
sometimes no I am a citizen of Ukraine and I am
бывает нет я гражданин украины и
interested in more Russians
заинтересован чтобы побольше российских
escaping from captivity it’s clear well you go
бежал из плена понятно ну вы
away and continue  this war, well, yes, to the
прочь и продолжать эту войну ну да до
bitter end, so that the knee of the
победного конца чтобы колено
proposed end you believe in the door and of
предлагаемого конца вы верите в дверь и
course already in the UK, don’t everyone believe even those
конечно уже в uk ли не все верят даже те
who doubted the first days and you
кто сомневались первые дни а вы его
watch it, you specifically choose Ukraine
смотрите вы специально выбираете украину
in chat roulette, but it’s better for us to just get
в чат-рулетке да нам же лучше раз попали
to Ukraine  and you support this war in
к украины а вы поддерживаете эту войну в
ukraine
украине
me and people 8 discussion discussing this
я так и люди 8 обсуждение обсуждают эта
toy for me the sense of a toy
игрушка для меня смысле игрушка
is generally youth cercare
это вообще молодежных cercare смеются
laughing at us and you yourself here you are by
над нами а вы сами вот вы по
nationality who is
национальности кто
like a savior because I hear yes
как спаситель потому что я слышу да
got
попала туда
there look and networks what  was once
вот смотрите а сети что же когда-то была
subjugated before the Russian empire I am grateful for not being subjugated as
благодарен за то что не покорили как
subjugation,
покорению
I won’t tell you  that this is a generation of
я вам не скажу что это поколение
machines since I gave a lot of things to us about how,
машинам раз я много чего нам дала о том
on the transition to another, here you know in
на переходе на другой здесь знаете в
these mountainous areas, because their impact is somehow
этих горную ведь их удара ведь как-то
business and you would not have survived, of course, no, of
бизнесе и вы бы не выжили доце нет
course, for any, and
конечно по любым и
many peoples would not have survived,
многие народы бы тоже не выжили в том
including  Georgia from it turns out an hour and
числе и грузию из получается часа и
Ukraine didn’t survive the water stone, why
украина не выжили вода камень а почему
why didn’t they survive without Russia
почему бы не выжили без россии
because you had a lot of
потому что у вас было очень много
people who wanted to take it to your special place,
желающих чтобы прибрать к себе в особый
this is Austria-Hungary bad, that is, it
это австро-венгрия плохой то есть
turns out if we were in the assalam of
получается если бы мы были в ассалам
Austria-Hungary this  it would be bad, but a
австро-венгрии это было бы плохо а
vassal of Russia is good, yes,
вассалом россии это хорошо да
but at that moment Russia had no
но тот момент у россии не было никаких
plans to make serfs out of you
планов того чтобы сделать из вас
, look coherently
крепостных не было смотрите связно
listened, and I know
послушали а я знаю
documentary facts confirm
документальные факты подтверждают
historically that there were even such inscriptions
исторически что были даже такие надписи
that
что
Ukrainians and
украинцам и
pigs you are just not right  walked-walked
свиньям вы как нельзя не то ходил-ходил
such a txt format by Ukrainians to dogs it was
такой формат txt украинцами собакам это
smashed wirst photo but this castle
разбили wirst фотография но этот замок
can be set and you can show a
можно ставить и можно показать
photo where Putin
фотографию где путин
hitler onts his eyes of a dog can be
гитлер онц его глаза собаки можно
shown  the photos are now photoshopped what
показать фотографии сейчас фотошопом что
merten wants, I have stated that
хочет merten заявлено у меня вот
look at the
смотрите
Russian empire, so that is, there was a
российской империи так то есть было
conquest of the Caucasus, there
завоевание кавказа
were punitive expeditions, by the way,
были карательные экспедиции вы кстати в
there were also punitive expeditions of the general on the network,
сети тоже были карательные экспедиции
purely my son’s surname
генерала чисто моя фамилия сына
will turn out, that is, it turns out all the same
получится то есть получается все таки
you are somehow forcibly joining
вас как-то насильно присоединение
to open a
открывать
meaningful plunger  melissa tv and look
смыслящий plunger melissa tv и смотрите
it has been open for a long time already something therefore there are
он уже давно открытый уже что-то поэтому
no sheets here why don’t you climb
не листы тут нет а почему не лезьте
look with extremists if the culprit
смотрите с экстремистами при виновник
has no look russia russia has already
имеет нет смотрите россия россия уже
launched I’m afraid the berserk is extra 5 otherwise
запустила я боюсь берсерк лишних 5 иного
says days well what was the agatha of russia
говорит дней ну что было агатой россии
we can talk about that  what happened, but we
можно говорить про то что было а нам
shouldn’t, they didn’t stretch it either, it
нельзя им тоже не растягивали там вот
was the USSR, it was Russian, sensors are being transmitted,
был ссср было российским передаются
we weren’t born, we all
сенсоры это мы родились не стал мы все
know something, and our ancestors didn’t develop,
знаю нечто а наши предки не развиваться
but why are we what this proverb
а то что зачем нас какой сейчас этот
is going
идет
on in the Caucasus now, or how
на кавказе такая пословица или как
such wisdom
мудрость такая короче
came shorter  someone someone
пришел кто то
said to Mohammed
сказал магомету
Mohammed you know the score about you from San
магомед ты знаешь счет про тебя из сан
accident h  what do you
аварию что что твоему
imagine and at the same time, while the saber
представь и в это же время пока и сабля
grinds its teeth and thinks what to do, the
зубами скрипит и думает что сделать
one that some third person goes and
тот который некоторые третье лицо идет и
says, well, all this is ours,
говорит ну все это наши
you know what about you and the stavsky,
ты знаешь что про тебя и ставского
well, everything that he said that he was your mother and
ну все что он сказал что он твою маму и
and your sister  together slay
и твою сестру вместе slay
somehow what is happening I think that now
как-то что происходит я думаю что сейчас
such a person is russia wear
таким человеком есть россия носите
russia takes ossetians you do
россия берет осетин ты
n’t accept look america small
не принимаю смотрите америками маленьких
xmod cameras about the world america you saw
камер xmod о мире америка вы видели
that america attacked it is necessary to sow and
чтобы америка нападала надо сеять и
for example but i see that yes it is america
например а я вижу чтобы да она америка
attacks the network before  us america somalia
нападает на сетью до нас америка сомали
like a valley that's exactly so much that's why
как долина вот именно столько вот почему
so why america is bad bad but
так почему то америка плохая плохая но
starting the eighth year 2008 before
начинающий восьмой год 2008 год до када
housing was the organizer of the attack on the
жилье на был организатором нападения на
southern vain days and wear this
южную суетные дни и носить эта
territory of georgia in georgia
территория грузии в грузии
stories and why this is not a phone then such
stories а почему это не телефон то такой
was the king  david was exiled again, but
был царь давид сослан еще раз а вот есть
you want to eat now, let's do it, when
вы хотите сейчас давайте так когда
Georgia
грузия получила
received, look at these territories if we
вот смотрите и эти территории если мы
are on fire with the southern network, yes, if I do
горим при южная сетью да если я не
n't  acre to ask to be transported, it was inhabited by
закроем просить возить она заселена
Ossetians more already in the twentieth
осетинами больше уже на двадцатом
century before the
столетии до
beginning of the twentieth resettlement, and so this
начала двадцатого переселение а так эта
territory of Georgia, I admit it is an
территория грузии это признаюсь
internationally recognized territory,
международно признано территория
you see you start instead of
вы видите вы начинаете вместо того чтобы
being against the imperialist, these
быть против империалистических вот эти
wars of Russia that are aggressive in Russia, you
захватнических в россии войны россии вы
see somewhere America that sits there
видите где то америку которая там сидит
your pronounce your surname write your
ваш выговорить ваша фамилия пишите ваши
surname your surname suffered from the Russian
ваша фамилия пострадала от российской
expansion yes when the copyrights of the expansion of the
экспансии да когда копирайтами экспансии
cloud were history began to from
облака было истории стали до от
Russian history that is,
российской истории то есть в ваш и ваших
Russian was cut out in your and your ancestors and you look at
предках вырезали русский а вы посмотрите
me, too, the countries of Russia the country of the Zaporizhzhya
я тоже стран россии страна запорожская
Sich from Russia suffered damage to the view
сечь от россии страдали damage вида
that the Swedes  there was no trace of allies with
чтобы шведов нет следа были союзники с
us
нами
this is with you before with us su taken our
это с вами до с нами су принятыми наш
water with us were at home the hall was against the
вода с нами были дома зал был против
eyelashes you will talk about russia
ресниц будете говорить про россию
russia is an enemy to us and the enemy of the ukrainian is
россия враг нам да и враг украинскому
not there i am the ukrainian people and you are
нет я и есть украинский народ а вы это
not an option but in you  Ossetians are thrown like
не вариант а в вот вас осетин кидают как
meat to die in Ukraine and
мясо умирать в украину и в это
we support this, we know  why are we there
поддержите мы знаем для чего мы туда для
why why are you going there you are there
чего для чего вы туда идёте вы туда
for now once again once again your goods
пока еще раз еще раз еще раз ваш товар
by the tip don’t run away endure now
за кончик не не убегайте терпите теперь
you are occupiers when you come to
вы оккупанты когда вы приезжаете в
Russian troops in ukraine we buy
российские войска в украину покупаем
load in georgia you were also this
загрузить в грузии вы тоже были эту
panel  and kissed in life you bypassed the
панель и целовали в жизни вы обошли
sinker of the Georgian people, by the way, this is
грузило грузинский народ кстати это есть
my people to find fault with all the people and you,
мой народ придраться всему народу и вы
together with Russia, attacked gas from
вместе с россией напали на газе из вот
this northern sense,
этой северная смысле
you attacked Georgia absolutely right,
вы напали на грузию абсолютно верно я
right now I’m insulting you from Kislovodsk ship
тебя щас корабль из кисловодска
and you will show your level of
оскорблять и вы покажете свое уровень
education you  they attacked Georgia, I sent mine to
образования вы напали на грузию я свой у
the fish sadly or pasted this on the clearing
рыб наслали на грустно или на поляну
- the
наклеил вот это -
most interesting thing yes I saw you
самое что интересно да видел вы
admit tell me who you recognize that
признаете скажи мне кто вы признаете что
yours tell your family the
ваш скажите вашу семью вырезала
Russian empire massacred you say that
российская империя вы говорите что
your family suffered
пострадала ваша семья
, this is slavery understand mental
вот это есть рабство понимать ментальное
slavery
рабство
tell me faith you were once a free
расскажи вера вы когда-то были свободным
people then conquered you were cut out
народом потом вас покорила вырезались
only in your relatives and
только в ваших родственников и вы
now you are not sitting  grandpa doesn’t run away until
сейчас сидите не не убегает дедуля до
the bars are sitting, you will hear all the peoples
сидят бруски будешь услышали все народы
up to the Caucasus, even that is, the
до кавказа даже то есть
whole Caucasus was conquered to the Russians
кавказ весь был покорён до российскими
harshly and read yes, all these
жестки и читайте да там вот эти все
Russian writers poets to us all sorts of
российские писатели поэты нам всякие
Lermontov and how they described the conquests of the Caucasus
лермонтова да как они завоевания кавказа
before it turns out instead
до описывали получается вместо того
of remembering those who fought  for
чтобы вспоминать тех кто боролся за
independence, they don’t
так они не
understand that Russia slaughtered them with entire
понимают что россия вырезала их целыми
villages,
селениями
a whole punitive expeditions were made to the
целый карательные экспедиции делали на
Caucasus and the same Ossetians, oh, he’s red that ladies,
кавказ и тех же осетин о он ред что дамы
here we are for Russia, and so on because the
вот мы за россию и так дальше потому что
Russian empire did
российская империя сделала с этими
very terrible with these peoples and she took from
народами очень страшно и она забрала у
them how  this is in Russian parts not honor and
них как это по-русски части не честь и
dignity on it they don’t even believe that
достоинство на нем они даже не верят что
they can be independent why
они могут быть независимы почему
iceland iceland in which three hundred thousand
исландия исландия в которой триста тысяч
people live damn it on an island in the cold
человек живет блин на острове в холода
go and she lives better than russia the
ходи и она живет лучше чем россия
standard of living is better than in russia on the
уровень жизни то лучше чем в россии на
gdp  per capita
ввп на душу населения
if they are rubbish yes there are more than
если они [__] да там больше чем в
three hundred thousand people in Russia a small country
триста тысяч населения маленькая страна
why is it also northern  oh ossetia can’t
почему тоже там северной осетии не может
be independent can not give money
быть независимы может не отдавать деньги
to russia but
в россию а
dispose of itself i.e. there
распоряжаться самим у себя то есть есть
are huge resorts there is a huge
курорты до огромные есть огромный
tourism potential there are
туристический потенциал есть
resources because there is mining
ресурсы потому что там горное
industry yes yes there are
промышленные да да бывают
all sorts of minerals everything is there but
всякие полезные ископаемые все есть но
russia takes it gives handouts somehow
россия забирает дает подачки каким-то
local
местным
overseer governor and I'm not
надзирателем губернатором и все я не
happy they are happy that they live in
радует они радуются что они живут в
some kind of such a
каком-то таком
radical state and they protect this
коренном состояние и они защищают эту
empire yes because they will be without
империю да потому что они будут он без
Russia we would cut each other
россии мы бы тут все друг друга
here yes that's it Russia save
перерезали да вот именно россия спасите
Russia cut him he says  his
россия перерезала его он говорит его
family up to his last name is a bunch, but without Russia
семью до его фамилия куча но без россия
, and follow him damn it, and so it’s just
ним и следовать блин и так это просто
nonsense that doesn’t get into your head
бред который в голову не вкладывается
how
насколько их зазомбировали
much they have been zombified, how much they don’t have their own
насколько они не имеют своего кого-то
sense of
ощущения
national dignity, there
национального достоинства есть на
are a lot of people in the Caucasus
кавказе очень много людей которые
who think correctly and understand that the
правильно мыслят которые понимают что
way  of them nations is separate from
путь их них наций это отдельная от
Russia who understand that freedom by the
россии которые понимают что свобода
people gives in  the opportunity to develop this people more and more,
народом дает возможность на и больше
and they are to be some kind of
развить этот народ а они быть каком-то
second-rate in some kind of
второсортным в какой-то
multinational empire here, and
многонациональной вот этой империи и
therefore those people who are fighting for the
поэтому тем людям которые борются за
freedom of the peoples of the Caucasus are directly fighting in one
свободу народов кавказа прямо борятся
way or another, the underground is fighting or is fighting
так или как-то подполье борется или
informationally you have a huge
информационно борятся вам огромнейшее
huge respect for you  the struggle is
огромнейший уважение до ваша борьба
very difficult, but do not forget that the
очень тяжелый но не забывайте что у
Ukrainians also once had a difficult
украинцев тоже была когда-то тяжелая
struggle in the twentieth century, the
борьба в двадцатом столетии
organization of Ukrainian nationalists
организации украинских националистов
fought for an independent Ukrainian
боролась за независимое украинское
state, and
государство и
then it also seemed like some kind of
это казалось тогда тоже какой-то
pipe dream, nothing, everything happened
несбыточной мечтой ничего все случилось
because the more people raised
потому что чем больше людей поднимает
these ideas in their own countries  in my head on my own flag, and
эти идеи у себя в голове на свой флаг а
the more people with pure hearts rise under this flag,
тем больше под этот флаг встает людей с
but this is all a slave
чистыми сердцами а вот это все рабское
class, she will very quickly then
сословие она очень быстро потом
go over to the side of the new government, yes, she will say yes, we have
новой власти да будет говорить да мы
always been for our people, yes, we
всегда были за наш народ да это мы так
pretended like that, even we are for Russia  therefore,
притворялись даже мы за россией поэтому
fight like tomorrow Shevchenko storms of thousands and
боритесь яко завтра шевченко бури тыс и
extortions glory to Ukraine glory to the peoples
поборы слава украине слава народам
caucasus and kim mike in the morning they
кавказа и ким майк утром это своей
called it theirs subscribe put like
назывались подписуйтесь ставте лайк
overestimate go to so jupiter wants the
завышает иду на так что хочет юпитер
matrix channel and subscribe for a
матрицей канал и подписывайтесь на
kilogram in the pass under the video solo grin
килограмм в пасе под видео соло гринь